He hurts her a lot.
And then, the next day, they both pretend like it never happened.
What do you do when he's hurting your mom?
He always yells at us to get out.
What can we do?
So you hide?
I understand that.
You're afraid, and your mom would want you to be safe.
It sounds like your mom is just trying to survive.
You know, people aren't all that different from animals.
Some are predators, and some are prey.
I told you his nice guy thing was just an act.
Well, please keep it down, or I'll have to call the cops.
Some people are afraid of getting eaten, so they run and hide from everything.
It's just one thing after another.
So what was that?
Did you seduce the neighbor, too?
Is that why he wanted to play hero?
Is there no man you won't let have a turn with you?
You're disgusting!
We can file for divorce!
You can remarry!
No!
Why should you get what you want?
Huh?
Why are you...
You made me a punchline!
I'll die before I let you take anything else from me!
Some want to kill and eat everything.
But not everyone stays the same as they were born.
Some people will evolve, become something new.
They're the ones who hunt predators.
They learn to fight and protect.
What kind of person do you want to be when you grow up?
What should we lift better?
What he wants to find?
What are you doing?
What could you do?
You're the one who does.
What are you doing?
How am I moving?
I've come to you.
How do you drive me?
How do you do it?
In this regard, are you?
How do youаешь?
How do you drive me?
How do you drive them?
For you drive me?
You're the one who is living.
How do you drive me?
How are you drive yourself?
How do you drive?
It's one who starts to take the answers.
How do you drive me?
How do I drive?
What are you drive?